Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I would like to do BDQ!
Also, this is a fire.
While Gotochi wanders in the woods...
Wandering?
He lit it for me.
Thank you very much.
The fire...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'd like to use the fire for a barbecue.
I'd like to enjoy a little barbecue.
First of all...
Let's cut up some vegetables.
Oh!
Cutting vegetables.
I see.
That's part of it, isn't it?
That's right.
So I'll cut the vegetables for you.
You're going to cut them?
Yes, sir.
I'll cut them.
Okay.
I want to peel the carrots.
Oh, no, no, no, no...
I'll stop immediately.
No, no, no!
I was told that in advance.
If you hold the knife in a strange way, I'll stop you right away.
I want to peel it.
I just want to cut here.
Good, good, good.
Good luck, good luck. We'll wait for you.
We'll make a fire.
You guys can keep it going. I can't cook.
I just don't.
How many slices of carrots do you cut up for the visit to the Daikoujin?
I don't know.
Carrots?
That's all I can do.
What's that?
Like the full moon cut.
Full moon cut?
Yeah.
I want you to do it.
Like in pork miso soup.
I want you to do the full moon cut.
I'd like to see it.
Half-moon cut? Full moon?
Crescent moon?
Crescent cut.
Crescent cut is very...
Ichioh-kiri.
Yes, I've heard of Ichioh-kiri.
But this...
If you want to grill them in round slices...
I think it's fine to cut it in rounds.
No, I think it's fine to cut it in rounds.
Thinly sliced so it's easier to catch fire.
It's very thick.
Much thicker.
Shut up.
It's okay. It's all right.
I think we should split this up a little bit more, don't you? Yeah, that's right.
Let's put this one over here.
Hey, if that's the reason, you wanna try it? You want to try it? I got it, I got it.
It's the jiggle-jiggle type.
This is the only one that's easy to pick up.
Let's go again.
You know, it's too late for that now.
So let's take a pause.
It's okay to slant it.
Sorry.
No, no, no.
It's too late, Takato.
Too late!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
This is terrible.
What? We're not going to win? Oh, my God.
I think we should just put the carrots on first.
What? Isn't that great? I'm so...
Right?
That sucks.
It's like a ufo, but it's not. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Hold me up.
I'm going to take the Tobu.
Carrots are delicious.
Let's go Kaname...
Don't give it to me like that.
I did my best.
Here you go, Kaname.
It's going to open up a bit.
Why did I have two?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's okay.
It's fine.
You're good.
It's good, right?
It's hard, isn't it? It's so hard.
It's so hard, it jiggles.
Oh, yeah, that's good! Is it good?
Let's cut off all the petals too.
Kousa, you've done well so far.
I did pretty well in the last half.
That's what I'm talking about. This is a lot of carrots for three people.
Let's lose right away!
But wait a minute.
I've eaten all the meat, just the veggies. Let's split the veggies and carrots.
OK.
Shiitake mushrooms.
Fast forward.
Okay.
OK.
You've already made the vegetable mushrooms, haven't you?
Oh, so it's all ready to go?
Yes, we are.
Okay, then.
Can we get started on the roast now?
Yes.
Shall we cook it immediately?
Shall we cook it?
It's better to cook something first.
Maybe we should just put them on.
I think carrots are hard, so you can put them on first.
Then green pepper.
Green pepper?
Green pepper, shiitake mushroom.
Okay.
Good luck.
We have all the ingredients.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to grill it right away and enjoy eating it with everyone!
Just in time to get some on!
It's really sticky!
Carrots, right?
They're like a group of carrot lovers.
Let's make carrots a little quito.
It's a nice painting.
They're roasting the carrots.
Wait, I think I've had enough.
There's no meat.
I don't think we can put any meat on the table.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now it looks like the Milky Way.
Maybe one more.
Okay, okay.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
That's really, really exciting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mushrooms and mushrooms
Shiitake mushrooms. Shiitake mushrooms.
Thanks for the carrot for me, Kousaku!
Yeah.
Okay, shiitake mushrooms for you next!
Cool!
Next, shiitake for you!
I want to eat the shiitake mushrooms you cooked for me, Konsaku.
I'll cook your shiitake.
What do you mean?
But it's not right.
It's not right.
Garbage.
You want trash?
I'm gonna put some meat on it.
Maybe it won't go with the meat, if it's stuck.
Maybe it's hard to cook the vegetables.
I'm going to grill the tawaine on the edge.
I'll put the meat in the middle and wait for the vegetables.
You see?
Can I ask you to surround it with vegetables?
Yes, ma'am.
Come on, it shows character.
Did you see that? Just now.
Now, this is a defining moment.
I fixed the face on the table.
Why?
He's very particular. Look, look, look.
He's letting go of everything he put down.
There's no moment to fix it.
He even changed the shape.
Look at it. Look at it all.
I know it doesn't look like a barbecue, but...
It's okay. It's okay.
It's good. It's good meat.
How is it?
It's not quite done yet. I'll be excited when it's done.
How much do you want to cook it?
We had a barbecue once, remember?
We did, a long time ago. It was an event organized by Jun's fan club.
It's different from barbecues in the city. Barbecues in a natural setting are more relaxing because there's more nature.
It's different. It's different.
The sheets are a little baked.
What do you think? What do you think it's going to be like?
Maybe not yet.
It's so-so.
It's just a little bit of barbecue sauce.
Still, doesn't it look like barbecue? They're all lined up.
This surroundings...
In a word, a carrot party.
I like it. I like the magic circle.
Magic circle with carrots.
The meat's starting to cook.
It's starting to sound good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's burning.
Right in the middle.
Yeah, let's wait for the middle.
But it's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
That's great.
Here comes the oil.
Kanawo looks tight.
I'll switch to you.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's all right. You're gonna cook it, right?
I think it's done. Here.
Oh, my God, that's so good.
You want some? You want some?
Yeah, you don't want to overcook it.
You're gonna eat it, right?
Oh, my God.
Let's eat it while it's still warm.
Bon appétit!
That looks delicious.
You like it?
Yeah!
Yum!
Oh, yum!
Oh, man, oh, man.
Uh-oh!
Go, go, go, go!
Bon appétit!
Yee!
Yum!
Ha!
Suku-suku! Scoop, scoop!
How hard is it to adjust the heat?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ah!
Ugh, just a little bit of sudsy.
Just shhh!
Aah!
My team!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
Shi-shi-shi.
Let's eat.
Come on in.
Can I go?
There's some kind of shiboshibo that's really good.
It's really good.
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy. I'm sure of it.
Oh, it's not open.
Okay, everyone.
Gentlemen.
What do you think? How do you like it? Well...
It's great, seriously.
The fact that you can eat while feeling the nature is great!
Hey! It's good! How is it?
I finally feel like the barbecue is here.
It's great!
I've already enjoyed it so much.
I know, right?
I haven't eaten yet.
Shiitake mushrooms are delicious!
They're really good!
I'm counting on you.
Shiitake mushrooms. A journey of bliss?
Yeah, it's interesting.
It's interesting.
I think there are a lot of things we can do because of this opportunity.
You're right.
You've never been outside before.
That's right.
It's really just a project.
So it's true, there's no such thing as a photo shoot outside.
In terms of outside, I'd like to do something athletic, too.
For sure.
In the summer, we'll have something like an athletic venue.
And then there's simply...
I want to ride a banana boat.
Banana boats.
I want to ride it.
I'm right on the river.
I want to go down the river on it.
There's rafting, right?
There is rafting, isn't there?
Boat rafting.
And you know what?
I coached the local soccer team.
You're right.
You only did it once.
To tell you the truth, we had a local soccer team.
It was formed right around the time of the World Cup.
So far, we have the following members
Masaya
We have many members who can play basketball.
Yes, basketball, Mr. Junyun.
And Tabitha can play too.
I can do it, too.
I went to play basketball with you.
Yes, you did.
I'm up at the observatory of our fan club.
You can eat.
Eat it.
Can I have shiitake mushrooms?
Well, that's the end of YuruCamp.
It was really like a loose camp, wasn't it?
I'm sorry for being so loose.
It was really great.
What did you think? What do you think about YuruCan this time?
I don't know how to say it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This visual is terrible.
This is bad.
Maybe it's a little too forward.
Wait a minute, maybe a little back.
Maybe a little too far back.
Oh, it's okay.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
That was weird.
It was like a Coke.
How was it? Once again.
No, really.
You can tell me all about it.
Not bad.
I mean, this is the first time I've had a barbecue with such a small group.
I've never had a barbecue with such a small group before.
I've never had a barbecue with such a small group of people in the real world.
It's not often that you get to eat
It's rare.
It was great!
It was great.
It's something you can only do when you're camping.
We were able to talk in a relaxed way that only campers can do.
I'm glad you had a good time.
It was a lot of fun.
When I think about what I want to do...
I can't stop coming up with new ideas.
That's for sure.
When I think about what else I want to do
I think about what else I want to do.
I'm thinking about what else I want to do
I'm thinking about all the other things I can do.
I'm thinking that the more I go out there
I thought that the more I go, the more fun the YouTube project will be.
I thought, "The more we go, the more fun the YouTube project will be.
I think we're a group that talks a lot at our live performances.
I think we're a group that talks too much at our live shows.
I thought it would be nice to have a more relaxed atmosphere.
I was looking forward to this project
I think we were looking forward to doing something fun and private.
Well, that's why I wanted to do this on YouTube, so I'm glad we were able to do it.
I'm really happy that we were able to do this and make it happen.
I'm also very happy that we were able to make it happen, and I'm looking forward to working with you in the future.
Gachi-Can?
Did you say "Gachikan"?
What's that thing you're talking about with Katsuto?
Dog
Yeah.
Fureai.
And then there's the one we were just banging on about.
You might be able to see it on YouTube.
It would be great if we could get comments like, "Hey, we did YuruCan," or something like that.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know... we've done YuruCamp, starting from the tent construction...
It's already a real camp.
That's where we'll start next time.
That's right.
Let's stay the night.
There's a bunch of people here.
Well, maybe next time we can do it with the other members, or with the seven members.
I'm sure you can watch it on YouTube, so please look forward to it!
That's all for now, the cause is me, thank you very much for YuruCamp!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
You're early!